<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SFYN TANK</title>
    <link>http://www.sfyntank.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SFYN TANK</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://www.sfyntank.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://www.sfyntank.com/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sfyntank.com/faq/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;faq:4a1318da06786ac52626178ca960109e&#34;&gt;FAQ&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-the-workshop-about:4a1318da06786ac52626178ca960109e&#34;&gt;What is the workshop about?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The SFYN Tank is about bringing people with food expertise and creative expertise together in order to critically think out solutions to food problems. It’s a test-run to potentially being a “think-tank” within Slow Food and a skills-training opportunity for people within our network to learn how partake-in and organize such workshops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-do-we-mean-by-social-design-workshop:4a1318da06786ac52626178ca960109e&#34;&gt;What do we mean by social-design workshop?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By “social-design,” we mean studying a problem that humans and their communities face&amp;ndash;understanding the needs of each entity involved in the problem and designing services or products that can resolve that problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;who-is-it-for:4a1318da06786ac52626178ca960109e&#34;&gt;Who is it for?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re eager for delegates within the Slow Food Youth Network to partake,
and we’ve invited creatives in the design field from Italian universities and industry, but the SFYN Tank is open to anyone who works within food and/or the creative sector that is interested in one of the nine issues, likes problem-solving, and enjoys working in a team!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-these-nine-issues:4a1318da06786ac52626178ca960109e&#34;&gt;Why these nine issues?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These issues surfaced when we sat down in April to try and hash-out the direction of our global Slow Food Youth Network. We prompted some of our delegates with a few simple questions, and answers surfaced from our South African, Ugandan, Japanese, Brazilian, Swiss, and Argentine delegations. From there, we realized there were some specific problems we could collectively work to resolve, and we wanted to create an opportunity to do so!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-a-co-working-space:4a1318da06786ac52626178ca960109e&#34;&gt;Why a co-working space?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Co-working is at the essence of the SFYN Tank: we want people from all sorts of disciplines to work alongside each other in order to learn from and teach one another. Toolbox officelab and co-working space seemed like the perfect home for such an occasion!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-tools-will-i-have-access-to:4a1318da06786ac52626178ca960109e&#34;&gt;What tools will I have access to?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fablab is the multi-tool laboratory within Toolbox, and they’re willing to give us access to some their instruments, like their 3D clay printers. Tankers will be able utilize some such instruments and/or software with instructions from Fablab volunteers during the prototyping portion of the workshop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;will-i-be-fed:4a1318da06786ac52626178ca960109e&#34;&gt;Will I be fed?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You sure will! Refreshments will be available all day, and a playfully delicious lunch will be provided by Ebible Co., an experiential food-events collective born from a talented group of friends and students at The University of Gastronomic Sciences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;do-i-need-to-bring-anything:4a1318da06786ac52626178ca960109e&#34;&gt;Do I need to bring anything?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We highly suggest you bring your favorite note-taking tool, whether it be a notebook, laptop, or tablet. Wifi is free and available throughout the site. Writing tools, post-its, and whiteboards will be provided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-do-i-get-there:4a1318da06786ac52626178ca960109e&#34;&gt;How do I get there?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Toolbox is housed in an industrial building behind the Porta Nuova train station. To get there&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Metro: We’re closest to the “Dante” stop on the metro, between Porta Nuova and Lingotto. After exiting the metro station, Toolbox is just a 7-minute walk away, and we’ll have signs up to direct you!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Foot: Toolbox is an easy 30-minute walk from Porta Nuova train station. If you exit left out of the train station, the street adjacent to Porta Nuova is Via Paolo Sacchi. Make a left and walk straight down that street for 20 or so minutes, till you intersect Corso Dante Alighieri. Turn left onto Corso Alighieri, and after just a few meters, make another left onto Via Egeo. Toolbox is at the end of the road!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Car: If you gotta come by car, we hope you’ll carpool! Utilize a
GPS to reach us, and paid-parking is abundant in the area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-will-i-walk-away-with:4a1318da06786ac52626178ca960109e&#34;&gt;What will I walk away with?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re not yet at a level to invite potential investors, and there is no prize for the best solution. We just hope to have you all practice this workshop process, connect, get inspired, and stay in touch, with the potential to realize some of your solutions inde
pendently. On the part of SFYN, we’ll collect and document all the produced work from the day, share with the network, and compile a more thorough proposal of feasible solutions to potentially work on within Slow Food in the coming year.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://www.sfyntank.com/program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.sfyntank.com/program/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;program:aebc7d6dace6c638857ad5a56a0b53b5&#34;&gt;PROGRAM:&lt;/h1&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>